{
    "subject": "resource/William_Alexander_McMaster",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London,_Ontario",
    "human_readable": "The birthplace of William Alexander McMaster is London, Ontario.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9507439732551575,
            "question": "How has London, Ontario changed since William Alexander McMaster's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9299277663230896,
            "question": "Where was William Alexander McMaster born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8476921319961548,
            "question": "What is the significance of William Alexander McMaster's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7741736173629761,
            "question": "Who was William Alexander McMaster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7090436816215515,
            "question": "Were there any notable events that occurred in London, Ontario during William Alexander McMaster's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4951305091381073,
            "question": "What is London, Ontario known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2912735641002655,
            "question": "Can you name any prominent people from London, Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28679871559143066,
            "question": "Is there a famous university in London, Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2748335897922516,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the history of London, Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2415686845779419,
            "question": "What are some interesting historical facts about London, Ontario?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birthplace of William Alexander McMaster is London, Ontario.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4064_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the history of London, Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4064_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a famous university in London, Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4064_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any prominent people from London, Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4064_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4064_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that the statement about William Alexander McMaster's birthplace is incorrect. \n\nHere is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, William1 McMaster was born circa 1790 in Edinborough, Scotland, not in London, Ontario. Therefore, the statement that his birthplace is London, Ontario, is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "William Alexander McMaster was born in Apr 1882 in Dromore, Sligo, Ireland, not in London, Ontario.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on the McMaster family history, tracing lineages and births primarily in Ireland and Australia. There's no mention of William Alexander McMaster or a connection to London, Ontario.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of London, Ontario as the birthplace of William Alexander McMaster in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention William Alexander McMaster's birthplace. Moreover, the given details are about William1 McMaster, who was born circa 1790 in Edinborough, Scotland, and his children. There is no information provided about a William Alexander McMaster or his birthplace being London, Ontario.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}